Hi, and this lesson, I will show you how to check that Chi-GPT is not trained on your data.
It's especially important if you use a free account, because in free accounts, this toggle
on by default, but if you use paid account, you shouldn't care about it, it's off.
So, to check it, just click on your profile, click on settings, data controls, and just be sure
that this toggle is off. When it's off, you're not allowed your content to be used to train
Chi-GPT models, which of course made Chi-GPT better, but if you don't want it, so you can just
toggle it off. Okay, this is everything I want to show you in this lesson. It's really important
for most of the users, and because they don't know how to disable it, and then just,
I share my data, and it's a try, it's trained on it, but now you know how to disable it. Okay,
see you in the next lesson.